Hello, I'm Ashanti Epps, and I'm the CEO and founder of A
Perfect Swing, Incorporated.
And I'm honored to be a part of the Celebration 120 Advisory
Committee.
2026 represents a historical milestone in golf's history.
Clearview Golf Course, known as America's Course,
will celebrate its 80th year of continuous operation
by the family of William Powell, a US Army veteran.
Similarly, the National Black Golf Hall of Fame,
founded by Harold Donovan, celebrate its 40th anniversary.
These two organizations have come together
to collectively celebrate this historical moment, 120 years
celebrating golf's black history.
We invite you to join us on Friday and Saturday,
October the 2nd and 3rd, at the historic Clearview Golf Course
in East Canton, Ohio, to celebrate this historic golf
moment.